

PERSONAL INFO

Portfolio:

https://turelyk-arsenportfolio.netlify.app/

Address:

L-4575, Differdange, Luxembourg

C Phone:

+352 661-870-688

☑ Email:

arsen.turelyk@gmail.com

In Linkedin

www.linkedin.com/in/arsenturelyk

LANGUAGES

English B1

German A1

Ukrainian C

Russian C

HOBBIES

Technologies

Science & data analysis

Traveling

CERTIFICATION

PhD certificate in chemistry

More than 15 scientific publications

Master's degree in chemistry

Bachelor of chemistry

ARSEN TURELYK

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I am a junior full-stack developer who recently graduated from a Full Stack Developer course. Although my education is in chemistry, after graduating from university, I started my career at a pharmaceutical plant as the youngest employee in one of the departments because my specialty did not correspond to the position. However, within 2 years, I became the head of this department and managed it for 10 years until I moved to Luxembourg more than a year ago. While here, I am improving my English language skills and have already reached a B1 level. I will continue to improve my skills to become a valuable member of your team.

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- I have experience in creating responsive designs using Figma and Adobe XD.
- Proficiency in programming languages such as JavaScript, Jquery, AJAX, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap.
- Familiarity with version control systems, such as Git.
- Knowledge of front-end frameworks and libraries: React, Angular or Vue.js.
- App and desktop framework: Ionic and Electron.
- Understanding of database management systems and experience working with SQL and MySQL databases.
- Strong knowledge of PHP and object-oriented programming (OOP) principles.
- Experience with back-end frameworks and libraries, such as Laravel.
- Knowledge of popular CMS platforms such as WordPress.

EDUCATION

2023

Full Stack Developer course

Cap4 Lab organized by ADEM from february to may

I have undergone intensive training in both front-end and back-end web development to enhance my skills as a full stack developer and feel confident in the competitive IT market. The course was created by Igor Marty and I was selected to participate after an evaluation on the ICT Start course and an interview with ADEM, which gave me the opportunity to continue my studies and pursue a career in this field.

English learning course

Walferdange Courses

English courses B2/B1

2022

ICT Start course

Digital Learning Hub Luxembourg organized by ADEM

Study HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

Volunteer Learning Programme

Digital Inclusion

Theoretical studying and practical work (repairing desktop computers, laptops)

Basics of Web Development & Coding Specialization

Coursera (author: University of Michigan)

Study HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

English learning course

Walferdange Courses

English courses B1/A2

2007 - 2010

PhD Chemistry

Taras Shevchenko Kyiv University

Chemistry of organic compounds

2002 - 2007

Master's Degree

Taras Shevchenko Kyiv University

Chemistry of organic compounds

EXPERIENCE

Head of Chromatographic Laboratory (R&D)

2013 - 2022

Kyiv Vitamin Plant

- Planning, organization and coordination of chromatographic laboratory
 work
- Supervising operations with equipment, calibration and verification of laboratory devices.
- Work on Agilent 1100, 1260 and 1290 HPLC systems (DAD, FLD, RID).
- Agilent 6890N with HS G1888, 7890 GC systems (FID and MSD 5977B).

Chromatographer

2011 - 2013

Kyiv Vitamin Plant

Analysis according to current documentation on Agilent 1100 equipment. Development of control methods according to the European pharmacopoeia.

Organic chemist

2007 - 2010

Research and production enterprise Enamine

Synthesis of new substances and analysis to prove chemical structure of these compounds for writing scientific articles and working on PhD "Heterocyclizations based on unsaturated bromoketones". Implementation and organization of the complex chemical syntheses.